RG 062:079, Town of Marlborough
Connecticut State Library
Town of Marlborough records
1836-1911, 1963
Connecticut State Library
Marlborough (Conn.)
3.5 cubic feet
Administrative, election, military, and tax records for the town of Marlborough.
RG062_079
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Marlborough was incorporated in May 1803 and was taken from Colchester, Glastonbury and Hebron.
Scope and Content
Administrative, election, military, and tax records for the town of Marlborough.
Index Terms
Alternate Creators:
Connecticut. Justice of the Peace (Marlborough)
Subjects:
Aerial photographs -- Connecticut -- Marlborough; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Marlborough; Elections -- Connecticut -- Marlborough -- Statistics; Voting -- Connecticut -- Marlborough -- Statistics; Justices of the peace -- Connecticut -- Marlborough; Writs -- Connecticut -- Marlborough
Places:
Marlborough (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1836-1911, 1963
  - T000252
    - Assorted town records, namely town meeting warnings, 1899-1911 (Box Box 1)
    - Town meeting records, 1900-1908 (Box Box 1)
    - Certificates of electors, 1836-1867 (Box Box 1)
    - Voters lists, 1902-1908 (Box Box 1)
    - Election returns, 1902-1906 (Box Box 1)
    - Candidates' expense statements, 1906-1908 (Box Box 1)
    - Appointments to town office, 1900-1911 (Box Box 1)
    - Town orders, bills and receipts, 1894-1906 (Box Box 1)
    - Military records, 1874-1899 (Box Box 1)
    - Writs of attachments and releases, 1898-1910 (Box Box 1)
    - Grand lists, 1897-1906 (Box Box 1)
    - Road bonds, 1893 (Box Box 1)
  - 2008-040
    - Aerial photographs, 1963 April 20; Creator: Robinson Aerial Surveys, Inc.; 81 photographs, 9 x 9 in. (Box Box 1)
      Arranged numerically. Photographs are identified in the upper right hand corner with the notation: "MAR-1-999" where 999 refers to sequence number.
      Not all numbers are present. Present are: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 97, 98, 99, 100, 116 (3), 117 (2), 118 (2), 119 (2), 120 (2), 121(2), 122 (2), 123 (2).
      These photographs are curled. Care should be taken when handling. Do not try to flatten.
    - Aerial photographs, 1963 April 20; Robinson Aerial Surveys, Inc.; 42 photographs, 36 x 36 in., mounted on canvas (Box Items)
      Arranged numerically. Photographs are numbered 1 to 32. There are also photographs numbered 8A, 9B, 9C, 9D, 15D, 15E, 15F, 16G, 16H, 16I, 21J.
      These are enlargements of the 9 x 9 in. photographs. The large format map number corresponds to the small format sequence number as follows: 1=99; 2=66; 3=47; 4=97; 5=64; 6=81; 7=33; 8=45; 8A=123; 9=95; 9B=122; 9C=unidentified; 10=62; 11=79; 12=9; 13=31; 14=43; 15=93; 15D=120; 15E=121; 15F=119; 16=60; 16G=118; 16H=unidentified; 16I=117; 17=77; 18=7; 19=41; 20=91; 21=58; 21J=116; 22=75; 23=5; 24=39; 25=89; 26=56; 27=73; 28=3; 29=87; 30=54; 31=71; 32=1.